Nice to meet you.
Sanetomo Narita's dear son...
So that's Mido!
Something wrong?
He was the researcher present
when I opened my Prime Right.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
All right, I'm leaving the indoor guard to you.
Roger that.
Gobo, how's it going over there?
Shinozakin says nothing fishy
is going on over there!
We can communicate with Sensei
through the Presentation Right...
Rika's with them, so they should be safe.
Mido, is it? You should know there are
two Prime Right owners here right now.
We just want to ask some questions,
but if you resist, we'll use
whatever means necessary.
It's information you want, right?
I don't mind giving you that, but...
You'll have to share your
current situation for me to talk.
Fine—
I'll tell him.
You watch out for any suspicious behavior.
I see. I suppose I'd expect nothing less
from Sanetomo's son.
Blessed with friends, opportunities,
and good luck, too. How wonderful.
Although, who knew... you hadn't
heard anything from your father.
What's that supposed to mean?
You still don't know?
Your father was one of the best
minds of the organization.
The only reason I obliged to his negotiations
was because I didn't think
I could outperform him.
But now look, like father like son.
You came all this way...
Although, I suppose most of it was
thanks to that man named Sudo.
So I was right about
his discernment after all.
You know Sudo Senpai?!
I was the one who stabbed him.
Pres...
Mido... Give us all the information you have.
As long as you don't get violent.
First question. Is our theory correct?
Mostly. You've done a brilliant job
solving the puzzle.
What parts did we get wrong?
Nothing important.
The way you arrived at your answer was
flawed, but it doesn't make any difference.
The Emperor is in Chiyoda. Is that right?
Right, indeed.
Tell us if you know more
specifically whereabouts.
The Emperor's in their ridiculous tower.
Exactly the kind of citadel
you'd expect from a kid.
A kid?!
That's right. The Emperor
is a 12-year old kid.
The Emperor's... a child?
The Emperor's tower is currently
surrounded by a huge number of corpses.
Corpses?
The Emperor's using their Rights to turn
them into puppets or, better yet, zombies.
There's tens of thousands of them,
making it impossible to even reach the tower.
On top of that, they've used the Prime Right
of Concealment to hide the tower.
It's invisible to the naked eye
outside of the ward.
Although, I can barely see it
with my Transillumination Right.
I knew it... The Emperor's becoming
neurotic about their defenses.
They may be a kid, but they're still
the Emperor. They have no opening.
Rights
There's a total of 666 Rights, most of which
are in the hands of the Emperor by now.
Rights
Emperor
But there's still a path to victory,
which is why I'm sharing
this information with you.
It would make it more
convenient for me, after all...
And in the end, I'll succeed
all of the Emperor's Rights.
Just as I thought, he plans
to steal the Rights altogether,
including the Recovery Right!
You saw how the bodies
and postboxes disappeared.
That's the Recovery Right.
Postboxes are recovered instantly. A large
volume of bodies takes about two days.
In comparison, the Succession Right
takes effect immediately!
Even if they could be revived, I'd be able
to use my powers the moment they die!
That's the merit to keeping me alive.
Consider me an insurance policy
to neutralize the Emperor.
Between a person that's capable of
discussions like myself and the Emperor,
whom do you prefer?
Don't worry 'bout it.
We won't kill you for now.
More importantly, this path to
victory... is it Sane's Prime Right?
Sanetomo Narita was truly
an exceptional mind.
He was able to assess the Camp's state
back then and determine its future course.
After the major breakout, subjects
were restricted to children.
And when the Recovery Right was
opened, the Emperor was born.
Sanetomo anticipated this turn of events
and smuggled out the Prime Right that
could act as the ultimate trump card.
That Prime Right is...
Exclusive Prime Right... Parental Authority.
Exclusive
Prime Right
Parental                        Authority
Parental... authority?
The only thing you need to do
is look the subject minor in the face
and declare its "parent."
Once a parent is designated, the minor
must obey the parent's orders.
Plus, all their Rights will be under
the jurisdiction of the parent.
Look the Emperor in the face and
declare your parenthood... And we win!
H-Hey, that's awesome if true!
For real!
No... think about it...
Kid or not, the Emperor wouldn't
lead someone to their grounds
when they could lose to them.
Mido's definitely setting me up.
Something about me meeting the Emperor
must give him an advantage.
There's no possible advantage that could
come from the Emperor defeating me, so...
What about if I defeat the Emperor?
Prime
Right
The Emperor won't be able to
exercise their Rights!
Then all that's left is to wait
for an opening to kill them.
Without Tasuketsu, Mido will
be able to act more freely.
He must be telling the truth...
I came here to engage
in constructive discussion,
knowing very well that you lured me
here to extract information.
Call it give and take.
You can decline if you want, but
there's really no other path left.
Now that you've learned
how to defeat the Emperor,
it's up to you what to do with them
after you seize control.
If you decide not to kill them
and monitor them instead,
you won't have to worry about
their Rights being turned over to me.
I'm fine with the simple possibility
of gaining that advantage.
An excellent bargain, don't you think?
Fine, I'm good with that exchange!
But only if you answer every
single one of our questions!
So greedy, but I don't mind. Hurry up.
You said the dead were recovered.
Have they all become puppets?
Who knows. You'll have to
ask the Emperor yourself.
What does the Emperor look like?
I haven't seen 'em.
Only researchers present at their lab tests
were supposed to know, but...
the damned fools held an event
to show off their success.
I assume anyone who was
present saw the Emperor.
Attending an event that risks leaving
an impression on the Emperor...
Foolish, isn't it? If they take a dislike
to you, you'd be the first to die.
I heard your end goal was to annihilate
the entire human race besides yourself.
Is that true?
Yes, it is. That's my ideal world.
Any other questions?
Just one more!
Gobo!
We'll use the Presentation Right to
contact you on that device when necessary.
Answer it no matter what.
Quite the demand...
Fine. I'll go along with your plan.
You sure, Sane?
The device we gave him was made
with Souma's Materialization Right.
Equipped with a remote control micro bomb!
We can trace it with
Gobo's Presentation Right.
If Mido strays from our command, we'll detonate
the bomb along with the device altogether.
Whoa... lethal stuff.
I've killed plenty of people
since Tasuketsu started.
I know my fate at this point.
I don't mind doing the dirty work.
Good. Mido's left the building
without any incidents.
Can you send word to Gobo?
All righty!
No, wait!
Huh?
What's up?
Iruga! When did he—
Thanks for the warm welcome,
Saneatsu Narita-kun.
What are you doing here?
Don't worry, I don't plan on hurting you.
I haven't seen Mido since then anyway.
You sure? He was here just a second ago!
Really? What a coincidence.
I came to give the Obedience
Right... to you, Narita-chan.
The Obedience Right?! To me?
But what about its owner?!
Like I said before, he's dead.
Ummm... I guess I'll explain.
So that's the gist of it!
Fine. I suppose we'll trust you.
Spoken like a true leader!
Commanding notes to secure
the Obedience Right itself...
The logic would check out.
I decided to give these envelopes
to you to keep hope alive.
This is our last chance to carry out
justice on behalf of Teppei-chan.
I want to see that through.
But if that justice doesn't really exist...
I'll kill off the entire race for good.
I'm counting on you, Narita-chan!
'Kay then, Narita-chan, come here for a sec.
This part is for your ears only.
I'm entrusting you with these
four simple commands...
which I'm going to teach you now.
Sane...
It's okay, I'll be fine.
R-Really?
Those are the commands in here?
That's right.
I'm gonna reiterate: these commands
can only be used once,
on the first person who sees them.
Use them wisely and don't screw it up.
See ya!
He disappeared?!
He probably used the Division Right
to divide the space around him.
Could you call over Omi and Gobo?
I've figured out our plan.
A-Are you sure about that?!
The Emperor is highly
aware of their defenses.
We have to go in with the assumption
that they've come up with a counter
for every possible attack.
This is our only shot if we want to
create an opening and win for sure.
I have a hard time
believing Ren Iruga, but...
It's all or nothing at this point, for real.
Why would the Emperor lead
an enemy like me to their grounds?
If they just wanted to kill me, they could.
I think they just want to meet me.
Once they're satisfied, then they'll kill me.
That's the Emperor's plan against me.
But of course, that comes with risks.
If I were to exercise my Parental
Authority, or come with one of you guys,
the Emperor could die or lose...
So the Emperor must have a way
of neutralizing even that scenario.
You mean we can't win by sheer strength?
Yeah, they must have a Prime Right that
blocks physical attacks, at the very least.
It's safe to assume they have measures
to counter my Parental Authority, too.
So there's no defeating them
with the Parental Authority.
The four of us have the most important roles.
I hate asking this of you, but...
Lend me your help with your life on the line!
Roger that!
Yeah.
Mm-yup.
The five of us!
Isn't that right?
Saaya! You were listening?
Don't leave me out, Saneatsu...
To think that I'd be out of the loop
while you're risking your lives...
What are you talking about, Saaya?!
There's no need for you to risk your life!
I'm not talking about
whether I need to or not!
We promised, remember?
We're in this together!
We'll defeat the Emperor no matter what!
No matter what that path might bring...
I want to live and fight together with you!
Fine...
Thank you, Saneatsu!
We'll only be able to keep the laptop
until the end of the day.
If there's another round
of Tasuketsu tomorrow night,
worst case scenario, we all die.
Our best opportunity is tonight!
Tonight, we'll defeat the Emperor!
So those are the puppets? Gross...
And... what's that?
If I'm right about Mido...
He should be well aware that the Emperor
likely has measures against
my Parental Authority.
He knew all along that our only option
to defeat the Emperor would be to kill them.
He was just throwing us
in the line of fire...
Mido will do whatever it takes to get
his hands on the Recovery Right.
Then, let's go ahead and
blow up that device, for real!
We can't do that.
If Mido dies and the Emperor recovers
the Transillumination Right,
they'll be able to see our weapon and plans.
That would mean game over for all of us.
And besides, I promised
that I wouldn't do that.
Promised? Whom?
Are you the leader?
I'm Saneatsu Narita. Welcome on board.
Hey, it's Shinozakin.
"Confirmed sighting of Emperor's tower."
"Location is within Hibiya Park."
"Height surpasses Tokyo Skytree..."
"Hibiya Park is covered with...
tens of thousands of puppets!"
Tens of thousands?!
You've gotta be kidding!
No worries. It's as expected.
It is?!
Time to explain the plan.
The four volunteers will split into two teams
and carry out a feint operation
to lure puppets.
Make sure to keep these cellphone on you
and watch out for Gobo's orders.
When there's an order to evacuate,
your mission's complete.
Disperse on the spot and
do as you please afterwards.
T-That's it?
Yeah, all we need is for you
to divert their attention.
However, the top priority is your safety.
That's kinda anti-climactic.
But what a relief....
That's it from me.
Saaya, could you take the four
of them to the break room?
Sure. Over here, everyone...
Now...
Before I get into the specifics of our plan,
I have something to declare just in case.
I want to take this opportunity
to name our team "Sugini"...
And that team will disband now,
effective immediately!
Huh? Disband?
Just accept it, please!
Is there anyone not willing to accept?
I reject!
Disband, right. Got it...
Was that really necessary?!
And we'll be creating two new teams:
Team Saneatsu and Team Yagihashi.
Team Saneatsu includes me,
Ryuta, Saaya, and Omi.
The rest will all work under Team Yagihashi.
The two teams will now begin
a joint operation.
Sounds like you're just making more work.
Just shut up and listen to the instructions!
And? What's this joint operation?
We'll raid Shinagawa Thermal Power Station
and Oi Thermal Power Station,
then temporarily cut the electricity
to invade the Emperor's tower.
I'll now explain detailed operation
plans and each of your roles.
Gobo, Omi, could you make sure
the cellphones are working?
We're really doing it, huh?
Yeah. Let's make sure we succeed
and take down the Emperor!
Saneatsu trusts someone
like me... I'm being useful!
This may be the biggest job of our lives!
I'm getting pumped up!
C'mon, let's go! Goki-hiko!
"Goki-hiko"?
Jeez...
Is that...?
The Emperor's tower...
They're coming over!
No worries, I'll use my
Visualization Right to dodge them!
It's quiet...
But how? Shinozaki-san said there were
tens of thousands of puppets all over town...
They must only be able to react
to things that come near them.
So that's why he has an army
but won't attack.
But isn't it weird that the paranoid
Emperor's fine with that?
The Emperor recovered bodies
and turned them into puppets, ya?
But what were they doing before
all those people died from Tasuketsu?
They were... alone? That can't be.
I thought about that, and
remembered something Mido said.
The researchers at the Camp.
Emperor
As Mido predicted, Tasuketsu
first began within the Camp.
Tasuketsu
Emperor
Researchers
Initially, puppets were created
from the bodies of researchers
and the Emperor went into hiding.
They then used the puppet researchers
to work on their behalf.
These "early puppets" must be
able to carry out complex orders.
Or, at the very least, there's gotta be some
puppets that can tackle complex tasks.
And they're the ones
managing the power stations.
Of course! It never occurred to me, but...
Power stations have to be managed
and operated by someone!
Does that mean they operate
the water and radio waves, too?
There's a chance these early puppets
also surround the Emperor...
Although there shouldn't be
more than a few of them.
A few?
Maintaining lifelines is a difficult task.
There's no other choice but to send
a large number of early puppets there.
Obviously, the Emperor's so strong
that they'd only need a
handmaid or servant with them.
He sure is a great leader to lean on...
Besides, these puppets have to
be excluded from Tasuketsu.
So that's one more thing we know
for sure about Tasuketsu...
The scope of Tasuketsu can be adjusted!
Which would explain
the first day of the test run!
23:29 PM!
It's time!
The Emperor set the laptop
recovery time to 23:55 PM.
Two left
You are currently looking at this screen
Tasuketsu announcements begin at 23:58 PM.
There's three minutes in between.
One left
Japanese citizens living in Tokyo Prefecture
Male or female
As a result of Tasuketsu, I'm...
Alive or Dead
This time is likely for recovery tasks
and review of submissions.
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
Prime Rights: 12 left
Rights: 45 left
40 years of age
Under or Over
1,081,990 people left
It's our best window to create
an opening for as long as possible.
We'll cut electricity supply at 23:55 PM
and invade the tower.
Operation will begin at... 23:30 PM!
Feint Operation!
Power Station Invasion Operation!
Operation
Begin!